fulltilt.com 2015-12-31

# Online Poker at Full Tilt Poker - Legal Information: Privacy

Your privacy is very important to Rational FT Enterprises Limited (referred to herein as " **Full Tilt** ", " **we** " or " **us** "), the owner and operator of the website located at www.fulltilt.com (the " **Site** "). We are committed to maintaining the confidentiality of the personal information collected by us in order to allow you to enjoy playing poker online at the Site, by safeguarding it utilizing the best in class software and hardware architecture, techniques, methods and procedures. We will comply with the terms of the Isle of Man's Data Protection Act 2002 when processing your personal information.

* **Consent to Privacy Policy**

By using the Service, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy and changes will come into effect immediately upon such change being notified on the Site. Your continued use of the Service constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any amendments. Our Terms & Conditions, see www.fulltilt.com/about-us/legal-information/terms, take precedence over any conflicting provision of this Privacy Policy. Unless otherwise defined herein, capitalised terms shall have the meaning given to them in our Terms & Conditions.

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to enable you to understand how we collect, store, use and safeguard your personal information and for you to understand your rights in relation to that information.

  * What information is collected and for what purpose
  * Deposit and withdrawal processing
  * Confidentiality
  * Limits of Confidentiality
  * Who receives your information?
  * Direct Marketing
  * Your rights in relation to your information
  * Cookies
  * Who are we?

* **What information is collected and for what purpose**

As part of the Site account opening process and to allow us to provide services to you, we will ask you to provide us with certain personal information, including your name, postal address, telephone number, email address and password as well as to certify that you are at least 18 years old or older in jurisdictions in which the minimum age for use of the Service is greater than 18. For the purposes of using the Service via the Mobile Software, you will be required to consent to the use of location-based services (LBS) by us to detect your geographic location. We may also use your information to verify your credentials from third parties including financial institutions, identification verification agencies and credit reference agencies for the purposes of us providing services to you. In addition, when you use the Service we store certain personal information, including information on your activity on the Site and information held on Devices (defined below) or systems that you use, to allow us to enhance the services that we provide to you. We, members of our group, our affiliates and third parties providing services on our behalf will use your personal information for various purposes such as:

  * to confirm financial transactions,
  * to provide services to you;
  * identification and vetting purposes;
  * statistical analysis and research;
  * research and development;
  * marketing, market research and customer profiling;
  * data analysis;
  * to comply with licensing and regulatory requirements; and
  * to analyse your credit and fraud risk.

We may disclose your personal information:

  1. if required to do so by law or by regulatory authority;
  2. if we believe in good faith that such action is necessary: 
    1. to comply with any law or comply with legal process served on us; 
    2. to protect and defend our rights or property;
    3. to any regulatory body or licensing body or authority;
    4. to third parties for the purposes of settling or making payment in connection with any wager;
    5. to any payment management or debt collection company engaged by us to handle payment and collection processes to and from Users; 
    6. to third parties who provide services to us or on our behalf; 
    7. to any third party that purchases us or our business or any part of us or our business;
    8. to credit reference agencies as described in the circumstances described below in this Section 2;
  3. with your consent;
  4. for the purposes of disaster recovery; or
  5. as set out in Sections 5 and 6 below.

We and other members of our corporate group may occasionally send you events and news information or information regarding new services and to provide you with customer support services. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletters, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter.

Where you fail to reimburse us for any chargebacks, denial or reversal of deposits you make, we may give details of your accounts and how you manage them to Credit Reference Agencies (CRA). The CRA will record the outstanding debt. This information may be supplied to other organisations and records will remain on the CRA file for 6 years after the date of the chargeback, denial or reversal of payment. The information will be used by the CRA to prevent crime, fraud, money laundering, verifying your identity if you, your partner, other members of your household, your business or financial associates apply for other facilities, monitoring the operation of accounts you may hold, making decisions for credit, credit related or other facilities, trace your whereabouts, recover debts that you owe, statistical analysis and system testing.

Your personal information may be processed by us, other members or our Group, our affiliates, our agents and third parties providing services to us, in jurisdictions outside of the Isle of Man and the European Economic Area. In this event we will comply with the terms of the Isle of Man's Data Protection Act 2002.

We will only use your name in publicity materials with your consent.

The name you register with us must be your own name. In addition, it is very important that you complete the account details with valid information, since it will be used in the course of validating financial transactions and the other aforementioned purposes. You are required to advise us of any relevant changes to your personal information.

Users are able to change account details by selecting an account option in the downloaded software.

* **Deposit and withdrawal processing**

In the course of making a deposit, Users will need to provide deposit method information (example: credit card number). This information in conjunction with your other personal information might be used to clear financial transactions executed by you with Full Tilt. You are required to advise us of any relevant changes to your personal information.

* **Confidentiality**

Full Tilt has undertaken substantial efforts to protect the confidentiality of the identity, preferences and other information it has collected about individual Users and will not knowingly allow access to this information to anyone outside Full Tilt, other than to the User or as described in this Privacy Policy. Full Tilt has made a substantial investment in its server, database, backup, firewall and encryption technologies to protect the information collected by Full Tilt. These technologies are deployed as part of state of the art security architecture, see www.fulltilt.com/real-money-poker/security.

You should also do your part in protecting your information. Your Login Credentials are confidential and you are obliged to keep your Login Credentials secret and confidential at all times and to use your best efforts to protect their secrecy and confidentiality.

* **Limits of Confidentiality**

Legally Required Disclosures: Due to the legal, regulatory and security environment in which we operate, Full Tilt may be required, under certain circumstances, to disclose personally identifiable information about our Users and we may not be permitted to inform you that we have done so. Full Tilt will use reasonable endeavours to limit such disclosure to the following: where Full Tilt believes in good faith that it is required to do so in response to a subpoena, warrant or other legal process; or where reasonably necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against persons or entities to preserve and/or enforce Full Tilt's rights. Further, we can, and you authorize us to, disclose your User identification, name, street address, city, state, post code, country, phone number, email, and company information plus details of financial instruments used to deposit and cashout to third party agents of Full Tilt or official government bodies as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy or other unlawful activity or activity that may expose us to legal liability.

* **Who receives your information?**

In addition to legally required disclosures as explained in this Privacy Policy, we may disclose your personal information to our employees, employees of other companies in our corporate group, our agents and to third party service providers who use your personal information to provide services to us in respect of your being a User with Full Tilt. 

We may combine your personal information collected from your use of the Service in accordance with this Privacy Policy with other information collected from you using other services operated by Full Tilt or any other member of the Group including, but not limited to online poker websites operated under the brands "Full Tilt", "Full Tilt Poker" (including the Site) and "PokerStars" as well as all products which are related or ancillary thereto, including mobile and social networking services. We will treat this combined information in accordance with, and will use it for the purposes set out in this Policy.

All recipients of your personal information shall be bound by applicable data protection laws to keep your personal information private at no less a level than that by which we are bound.

* **Direct Marketing**

We may use your email address and phone number for the purpose of providing you with news, promotions and other marketing offers from our Group. We may also share your email address and phone number with our marketing partners for the purpose of providing you with marketing offers. Out of respect for your right to privacy we have provided you with an easy means by which you may stop receiving marketing offers via email and telephone from us or from our partners and affiliates. You may request at any time to no longer receive such offers by changing your subscriptions through the Email Control Panel in the My Promotions section of your downloaded software or by sending a blank message with the word "Remove" in the subject area to [support@fulltilt.com](mailto:support@fulltilt.com). If you request to discontinue receiving these offers we will remove your details from our marketing distribution lists and from any future lists we may share with our marketing partners. However, you may need to unsubscribe separately from marketing offers sent by partners who have received your contact details from us prior to your request to be removed from these lists.

* **Your rights in relation to your information**

We aim to keep our information about you as accurate as possible. You can write to us at any time to review, change, obtain a copy of your information or have your details altered or corrected in accordance with your rights under the Isle of Man's Data Protection Act 2002 and in this event we may require evidence of your identity. In order to contact us regarding your information please email [support@fulltilt.com](mailto:support@fulltilt.com). We may in certain circumstances levy a small charge to cover the cost of administration regarding any request made by you in this regard.

* **Cookies**

Cookies are text-only strings of information that are downloaded to your personal desktop, laptop computer or mobile device (each a " **Device** ") when you visit a website. They are then sent back to the originating website on each subsequent visit, or to another website that recognises those cookies. 

Cookies are very useful and are used for many different purposes. These include allowing you to navigate between pages efficiently, remembering your preferences, and generally improving user experience. Sometimes cookies are used to help ensure that adverts you see online are relevant to you and your interests. We use cookies in order to track referrals to our websites, to remember your preferences, and to generate anonymised statistical data, which we use to improve the user experience on our sites. We also use cookies to measure the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns, to limit the number of times you see an advertisement, to remember that you have visited a website, and to provide advertisements that are more relevant to your interests.

Detailed information about cookies and how we use them on the Site may be found in our Cookie Policy, which also describes how you can turn off cookies or control which cookies are set on your Device (see in particular the section headed 'How to manage your cookie settings').

* **Who are we?**

Rational FT Enterprises Limited  
Douglas Bay Complex  
King Edward Road  
Onchan  
Isle of Man  
IM3 1DZ  
Privacy Policy last revised: 8 July 2014
